PABLO DE JESÚS

Full Stack Developer

pag753@gmail.com

<u>+52 1 238 133 60 66</u>

in	linkedin.com/i	n/paq75

github.com/pag753

codepen.io/pag753

pag753.000webhostapp.com



 \odot

CAREER SUMMARY

Software engineer with more of two years of experience in the backend part and frontend using PHP technology and its Codeigniter and Yii2 frameworks. Participating in information management projects in databases. I am willing to learn more and use other technologies especially in JavaScript, Python and Ruby.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Alphacredit

Julio 2020 - At present

Nodejs, Java and .Net Core developer in the company.

Description

Responsible for developing Node.js, Java and .Net Core processes in the company.

Technologies used:

Node.js Java

Spring boot

.Net Core

Full Stack Developer

Grupo Salinas

March 2019 - June 2020

Java, Vue.js and Python full stack developer in the company.

Description

Responsible for developing REST services and web portals for the management of the company.

Technologies used:

Spring boot

Struts

jQuery

HTML5

Vue.js

Full Stack Developer

TecNM / Instituto Tecnológico de Tehuacán

September 2018 - December 2018

Responsible for full stack development and database of the module 'didactic instrumentation' for use by all teachers of the National Technological Institute of Mexico.

Achievements:

Before the teachers made the didactic instrumentation in programs such as "word", following specific standards and formats, but now:

- Filling data is fast, intuitive and effective.
- At the end of the capture the teachers obtain the didactic instrumentation in a PDF complying with the norms and formats required and the confidence that everything they wrote and saved is in a database.
- The document once generated can be consulted or edited on the platform when and where they want from a web browser and with an internet connection.

Technologies used:











Bootstrap 4



Web Developer

February 2018 - July 2018

Responsible for full stack development and database of platform for the management of laundry process in the company 'Lavados Especiales' from Puebla city.

Description

Platform for automate in efficiently way the control of laundry processes and the company administration with the implementation of the project to obtain a better fastest and internal control.

Technologies used:

PHP 7

Codeigniter

MySQL

jQuery HTML5

Bootstrap 4

Data Tables

SKILLS AND TOOLS

Languajes PHP JavaScript Python Java C / C++ / C# **Frontend** jQuery Bootstrap HTML/CSS Vue.js **Backend PHP Frameworks** Node.js Python/Django Java/Spring Boot

EDUCATION

Git FontAwesome

Others

Computer Systems Enginer

TecNM / Instituto Tecnológico de Tehuacán

Linux

2014 - 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Technology Associate

Software Development Fundamentals 2015

Microsoft Technology Associate

Database Fundamentals

AWARDS

▼ State programming competition

In the <u>IT of Puebla</u> on April 22, 2016. Winner of the third place in the intermediate category.

The National Student Event of Technological Innovation (ENEIT) 2016

National stage in the IT of Pachuca from 22 to 25 November 2016 by the project "Enerluz".

TENEIT 2016

Regional stage in IT of Gustavo A. Madero in Mexico City, from 20 to 23 September 2016 by the projects "Enerluz" and "Autosilla". Winner with "Enerluz" project.

LANGUAGE

Spanish (Native)

English (Intermediate)

INTERESTS

Reading

Swimming

Watching movies

VOLUNTEER

Full Time Missioner

Misioneros Servidores de la Palabra

April 2011 - September 2013